[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[Abyss]
Has Feiyang joined another team?
[Feiyang]
No.
He's just busy with family matters.
He's stepping away
from the game for good.
[Group Management]
[Mr. Han] [Feiyang] [Wei]
Our Mr. Han is so righteous!
If you're so considerate of others,
why don't you give your clients to others?
Why only give them to Feiyang?
Isn't it because you two are in cahoots?
Do you have a conscience?
If Feiyang hadn't brought you in,
would you be where you are today?
And now you're holding
a grudge against him?
Wei, I didn't pick a fight with you.
Mom, aren't you on duty?
Why are you back at this hour?
My stomach hurts, so I took time off.
Have a seat first.
Go pour me a glass of hot water.
Okay.
Here, Mom.
Oh my.
I feel much better after
drinking some hot water.
Why did your stomach suddenly hurt?
Did you eat something cold?
I was spooked!
Two police officers suddenly
came to the hotel.
They called everyone to
the duty room for questioning.
I said my son is a police officer
and we are on the same side.
But they ignored me.
What did the police ask?
I was just about to tell you.
That Song we mentioned the other day,
the guy from my workplace?
He died!
What?
Song Laifu is dead?
Exactly.
I even greeted him this morning.
When I heard about this,
I thought of your dad back then.
He was fine in the morning.
We compared his hair
with the skin flakes found under
Liu Xiaohua's fingernails.
The results
didn't match.
[Episode 4]
The deceased, Song Laifu, 54 years old,
[Deceased: Song Laifu] [Age: 54]
A resident of Gaobeizhai Village,
Longhua County,
in the neighboring city of De'ermu.
He worked as a security guard at
Huangzhiyuan Hotel's carpark.
Unmarried, no children.
He lived in the hotel's staff dormitory.
It was 3 migrant workers
from a nearby construction site
who filed the report.
Based on the time of death,
they are not likely suspects of the crime.
We immediately
went to Huangzhiyuan Hotel
and retrieved the surveillance footage.
We found that at 10:07,
Song Laifu received a call.
He looked very unhappy,
stepped on and broke the mop handle,
and then left.
[Camera 01]
We checked Song Laifu's call records.
Two numbers called him once each,
at 1:03 a.m.
and 10:07 a.m.,
as captured by the surveillance.
Between the two calls,
[Time of Unknown Call]
Song Laifu was on duty at the hotel.
One call was from an unregistered number,
and the other
was from a public phone booth
near People's Square.
[People's Square]
There is a large flow of people here,
[Phone booth near People's Square]
and the phone booth
is not within the surveillance range.
We can only slowly investigate
to see if there are any witnesses.
Chief Tu.
If the call was made by the suspect,
it means he was well-prepared
and it wasn't a spur-of-the-moment act.
Did Song Laifu have any enemies?
The hotel staff all said
that Song Laifu was quite introverted
and didn't interact much with others.
The only person he had a conflict with was Xin Jiran.
Xin Jiran.
According to the hotel's duty staff,
Xin Jiran, Song Laifu,
and a female hotel employee named Chen Chunli
were involved in a romantic dispute.
He even got into a confrontation with
Song Laifu over this.
Xin?
He's only been out for a few years, right?
In the past, he and Ganzhe
caused the most trouble.
Is it that hard for you to
watch your diet?
Do you really have to be
in agonizing pain to feel good?
Gout won't kill you.
If I can't eat or drink all day,
life is meaningless.
Okay, okay.
Your sister-in-law happens to
be in Beijing.
I'll ask her to bring you
some special medicine.
Anyway,
regarding Xin,
I don't believe
he would kill someone over a woman.
Yes, Chief Tu.
The name Chen Chunli
shouldn't be unfamiliar to everyone.
She was the last victim of the 3/12 Case.
It has to be 7 or 8 years since
the 3/12 Case, right?
To be exact, it's been 8 years
and 7 months.
Over the past 8 years,
I've been using my spare time
to repeatedly scrutinize the case
and look for a breakthrough.
No matter how long it's been,
we can't let the suspect
get away with it.
Did you all hear that?
Learn more from Comrade Fanjie.
You,
especially you,
stop fooling around all day.
Any objections?
No, no, no.
At Song Laifu's place,
did you find anything?
[Recipient: Song Laifu]
Song Laifu received a
local package
sent 3 days ago,
but we don't know what's inside.
Judging by the shape, it looks like
a book or a magazine.
His roommate Wu Jianxiong said
he doesn't usually shop online
and barely knows how to use a computer.
The sender is Xiaofei,
[Recipient: Song Laifu]
with no return address.
The sender's address is
this courier station.
The sender must have
dropped it off in person.
This looks like my handwriting.
[Recipient: Song Laifu]
I remember now.
That day, this person came with a dog
and startled me.
Male or female?
What did they look like?
How old?
Male.
A bit taller than me.
He looked quite young,
probably around my age.
He went out of his way to
a courier station
to send a local package,
and then left a fake phone number.
[Name: Song Laifu]
This is very suspicious.
Keep a close eye on this clue.
Don't let up.
Yes.
Comrades.
First, find the crime scene
as soon as possible.
Get the surveillance footage from
the businesses
near the phone booths on
both sides of Kangfu Road,
and check it carefully.
Second, find Xin Jiran
and figure out where he was
during the time of the crime.
Third,
question all the employees
who had contact with Song Laifu,
especially Chen Chunli,
and see if we can find anything new.
Okay, I'll arrange it.
Tipping someone off?
Caught you red-handed, didn't I?
I'm not going home tonight,
so I'm calling my wife.
You think everyone is
as heartless as you are?
You're pretty impressive.
At your age,
you are still reporting to
your wife every day that
that you aren't out cheating.
How impressive!
Why does everything you say
sound so awful?
Help me change this.
Gently. Gently!
Bear with it.
Please peel.
How ruthless!
Your injury hasn't healed yet?
It was healed,
but you are injuring me once again.
Why apply a plaster if it's healed?
You have what the internet calls
a contrarian personality.
What can I do?
In our line of work,
we have to question everything.
If you see Xin Jiran,
tell him
to come to the station early
to explain things clearly.
He shouldn't let what
nobody wants to see happen,
and even get you involved.
You care about me.
I don't care about you at all.
I care about our police station.
For so many years,
we haven't recruited
a single good prospect.
Us old guys
have no choice but to hold on
if we can.
[Save water]
What are you doing?
What are you doing sneaking around?
You scared me.
Police!
What the hell? Don't move!
Keep your distance!
O-Officer.
Do you know the person in this room?
Yes, Officer!
Xin Jiran.
Male, 51 years old, sells dates.
He leaves at about 7:00 a.m.,
and comes back after 8:00 p.m.
He definitely didn't come back today.
Why?
Because the soundproofing here is bad,
and my hearing is good.
I can hear everything.
I haven't even asked you anything yet,
yet you're answering so clearly.
We were cellmates in prison.
I even found him
this apartment he is living in.
But what he does in there every day,
I have no idea.
If he's doing anything illegal,
please investigate it thoroughly.
It definitely has nothing to do with me.
Do you need me to open the door for you?
You have the key?
No need for a key. This door is broken.
Please come in.
What a fuss!
[Camera 01]
[Calling: Elite Student]
Who is calling in the middle of the night
and you're not answering?
Xin Jiran?
Bet a hundred bucks?
Why are you such a bore?
Hello.
Song Laifu is dead?
How did he die?
Is it related to what we're investigating?
Didn't I tell you?
I have an urgent case tonight
and have to work overtime.
My colleagues are all here.
I can't just slip away.
Understood.
Contact me when it's convenient.
Wang Tao said he can't find
Xin Jiran anywhere.
Could he have fled to escape punishment?
You haven't made any progress in
investigating cases,
but you're sure eager to
hand down convictions.
Zhao.
I advised you a long time ago
not to always protect Xin,
but you just wouldn't listen.
Now that you've caused such a huge mess,
how are you going to clean it up?
Do you really think
Xin would have a petty feud with
a parking lot attendant
just because of a woman,
and even kill someone?
Don't act like you're all righteous
whenever Xin comes up in conversation.
It's annoying to watch.
If it has nothing to do with him,
why did he run?
I'm asking you, why did he run?
Have you been a cop for so many years
for nothing?
Doesn't wanting to avoid people
necessarily mean he's guilty?
Who wants to be escorted back
by old colleagues with great fanfare?
Even if there's no evidence,
will you let him go?
Is he crazy?
Does he like being locked up in there?
I didn't realize before
how good your relationship with Xin was.
How come you guys are allies now?
[Camera 01]
I just want to solve the case.
Who doesn't want to solve the case?
Look,
you still say you're not helping Xin.
When my Zhao Ying was little,
Xiaoliang took good care of her.
She also liked Xiaoliang very much.
After Xiaoliang died,
Zhao Ying was very disappointed.
Since then, I feel
she no longer worships me
as her police father.
Maybe the child has grown up?
Hello?
It's me, Big Red Date.
Song Laifu is dead.
I heard.
What exactly happened?
Who did it?
I don't know.
But the police are looking for me.
If it's convenient,
let's meet at the usual place
at 9 p.m. tomorrow.
Why are the police looking for you?
Something happened.
It's hard to explain
in a few words right now.
We'll talk when we meet.
Don't tell Zhao Ganzhe
that I contacted you.
It will put him in a difficult position.
[Huangzhiyuan Hotel]
Hurry up! We're just waiting for you two.
Alright, since everyone is here,
I'll get straight to the point.
Song Laifu had an accident outside.
The police will be in
the staff lounge later
to question you one by one.
Our boss has said to
answer whatever they ask.
Tell the truth,
and don't try to outsmart.
What's wrong?
Must I go?
I was already questioned once yesterday.
Besides, I'm not familiar with Song.
Why do you have so many complaints?
Our boss is being questioned
inside right now.
What else do you want?
Song?
Yes.
An old employee.
But I'm not familiar with him.
As you all know,
I have quite a few businesses.
I rarely come to the hotel,
let alone pay attention to
a nighttime watchman.
Mr. Li, you must be really wealthy.
Huangzhiyuan Hotel
is considered the best hotel
in our county,
right?
And yet, to Mr. Li,
it's a business he looks down upon.
You're joking, Captain Fan.
It's not about looking down on it.
No matter how small a fly is,
it's still meat.
It's just that the hotel
is easy to manage.
I have two real estate projects
in Gucheng,
which are much more complicated
than running this hotel.
Our county leaders are paying
close attention to these projects too.
I'm not trying to elevate myself
by saying something like this.
Since I made a special trip here,
I'm trying to show my proactive attitude.
I hope you can catch the murderer soon.
That way, I can also
give an explanation to all the employees.
Who do you think is closer to Song Laifu?
You can ask Manager Zhang.
Song is under his management.
If he can't explain it clearly,
that's a dereliction of duty.
Tell me, and I'll deal with him.
[Staff Lounge]
No need to see me out.
Come in.
Call Chen Chunli next.
Okay.
How did you handle this?
[Staff Lounge]
How did you end up attracting the police?
I don't know either.
What's going on with Song?
Huangshui Jiayuan is about to be
put up for sale.
If it affects that,
who will take the blame?
You or me?
After the police leave,
hold a meeting for all staff.
Emphasize that
Song Laifu died outside.
Am I clear?
Alright.
If anyone dares to talk nonsense
and affect my business,
I'll make their life a living hell.
Then, Mr. Li...
should I fire Chen Chunli or...
I don't care.
Clean up your own mess.
If you cause any more trouble,
dig a hole and bury yourself.
Yes, don't worry, Mr. Li.
This won't happen again.
He and I are just ordinary colleagues.
We don't have much contact.
But I haven't heard of any problems
with him.
Many people say
he pursued you.
I can't control what he thinks,
but I am definitely not interested.
We only have one microwave
in the staff lounge.
Every time we eat,
there are over a dozen people
lining up to heat up their food.
When I get impatient,
I go to his security booth
to borrow his small stove.
Did Song Laifu say anything about
you borrowing the stove?
He's quite amiable.
Amiable?
When he gets angry,
he looks like he wants to kill someone.
Is there any specific incident?
I'll tell you,
but don't tell anyone else.
Otherwise, they'll wrong me
and say I'm gossiping even in his death.
Don't worry.
Everything you say in this room
is strictly confidential.
Xin Jiran has been
causing trouble at the hotel lately.
Do you know why?
I... think I know.
He just wants to investigate that case.
So he keeps coming to me,
asking this and that.
But whatever I know,
I've already told you.
I have nothing more to say.
I didn't dare admit to the hotel
that he was looking for me.
Was there any bad blood between
Song Laifu and Xin Jiran?
I don't know about that.
But I promise there's no
love triangle or anything.
I'm not close to either of them.
If you want to ask about Song Laifu,
I think you can ask Zhang Chengguo.
Your manager?
That day when I passed by the staff lounge,
I heard them chatting inside.
Song Laifu was hired by Zhang Chengguo.
They must have known each other for years.
I hired Song.
Before,
he was working at a friend's
construction site.
When I got off work and had nothing to do,
I would often go to their shed
to play cards with him.
That's how we got to know each other.
Later,
he said the work at the construction site
was too tiring
and asked me to find him an easier job.
My security post happened to
be short of hands.
So I told him to come and give it a try.
It was just a small favor.
So why not, right?
What’s Song Laifu’s work ethic like?
Did he make enemies with anyone?
He was good.
His attitude was really good.
He took work seriously too.
As for making enemies,
I don't think he would.
Song was very honest.
He talked little
and worked steadily.
He wasn't the type
to actively look for trouble with others.
At least that's how it seemed to me.
On the day of Song Laifu's accident,
he kicked and broke a mop handle.
It looked like he was
going to fight someone.
Do you know who he was looking for?
That happened?
Let me guess.
He probably went to find that drunk guy.
What's his name... Xin something?
I heard they had a grudge.
In your opinion,
besides hotel colleagues
and guests,
did Song Laifu had contact with
any other outsiders?
Very rarely.
We have a cleaner named Sun Yuhua
in our hotel.
Her son talked to Song a few days ago.
I just remembered.
I thought it was strange at the time.
I wondered how these two
could even have anything to talk about.
[Employee Record Form] [Sun Yuhua]
The cleaner's son?
What's his name?
His name is Li Cheng.
What is the relationship between
your son Li Cheng
and Song Laifu?
What relationship?
They don't even know each other.
Why would my son ever get involved in
matters of murder and arson?
What's going on?
Don't panic. We're just asking.
Someone saw your son talking to Song Laifu.
So what if they talked?
So what?
We are talking right now.
If you go out and get hit by a car later,
does it have anything to do with me?
-You...
-What are you talking about?
Sit down.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Officer, I didn't mean to curse you.
I'm just so angry.
This is ridiculous.
No need to explain.
Answering questions properly
is the best way to help your son.
Officers,
whoever mentioned my son to you
must have bad intentions.
Don't let such people mislead you.
Let me analyze this for you.
At the beginning of the year,
Song Laifu and Chen Chunli,
they had a pretty good relationship.
About three months ago,
Xin Jiran came out of nowhere.
The one who's drunk every day.
Chen Chunli had a change of heart.
She stopped talking to Song Laifu.
Song Laifu must have been angry.
He must have been frustrated.
He kept asking around
where Xin Jiran lived.
Until yesterday,
he finally found out.
He grabbed a weapon and
went to settle the score with Xin Jiran.
Unexpectedly, this drunkard Xin Jiran
was very agile when he wasn't drinking.
As a result, Song was killed instead.
That's probably what happened.
That's right. Let me tell you,
that must be it.
Case closed.
[Welcome home]
Mom.
You're finally here.
Why did the police call me here?
It doesn't matter.
At first,
I was very unhappy
that they dragged you into this.
Then I thought about it.
Wait, isn't this an opportunity?
You have to seize it.
No, no, Mom.
What opportunity?
I don't understand.
The two police officers you'll see later
are both leaders of the county's
public security bureau.
Just win over either of them,
got it?
They called me here
just to ask some questions, right?
Trying to suck up to them
would be inappropriate, no?
Is sucking up all that I
have ever taught you?
I have already paved the way for you.
Song's case is not complicated.
With just a few words,
I sorted it all out clearly.
They might not say anything,
but they definitely admire me
in their hearts.
Mom, you're amazing.
I am amazing.
Let's go.
Let me tell you.
Don't laugh! Be serious!
Come in.
You know why we called you here, right?
My mom said the hotel security guard,
Song Laifu,
had an accident.
I just had a conversation with Song Laifu
a few days ago.
You want to know
what I talked to him about that day.
You intentionally struck up a conversation
with Song Laifu, right?
Yes.
A while ago,
I saw a man named Xin Jiran
causing a disturbance
while drunk in the hotel lobby.
The manager called the police
and had him taken away.
Later, I heard he often comes
to make trouble,
and the police can't do anything about him.
I think this issue needs to be solved
from the root.
After asking around,
I learned that Song Laifu and Xin Jiran
have some conflicts.
So I took the initiative to
approach Song Laifu,
wanting to understand the situation
and see if there's any way
to resolve the conflict between them.
What does this have to do with you?
Although it will be two months
before I officially start working
as a police officer,
I have this sense of responsibility.
Besides, my mom works at this hotel.
Someone causing trouble
is a safety hazard for her.
Not bad.
Then did you figure out the conflict
between Song Laifu and this Xin Jiran?
Not yet.
But I think
it's definitely not just
a relationship dispute.
Reason?
Xin Jiran has absolutely no
intention of pursuing Chen Chunli.
His drunken disturbances
only caused trouble for Chen Chunli
and increase her stress.
Of course,
it's also possible that his
personal understanding of love
is somewhat skewed.
But I asked around carefully.
Xin Jiran used to be a police officer,
and his family was ruined
because of a case.
This case has not been fully solved
to this day.
So I think
Xin Jiran's motive to investigate the case
is far greater than pursuing a cleaner.
How did you know that
Xin Jiran used to be a police officer?
Xin Jiran's neighbors know some things.
I spent a little money
to find out all this.
Not bad.
Okay.
Very good.
Zhao, no questions, right?
No.
Not at all.
Thank you for your cooperation.
We'll stop here for today.
I also hope to see the day
you officially join the police force soon.
Thank you, Sir.
Okay.
I'll be going then.
Okay, let's go.
Zhao,
this young man is not bad.
Look,
he's quite smart, isn't he?
He's responsible and filial.
How great is that?
This kid is all talk and no action.
Not that great.
What's wrong with your judgement?
This is why
other places can recruit good people,
except our police force.
Not a single smart one.
[Public Security]
[Camera 01]
This piece of plastic
looks very similar to the one found at
Song Laifu's crime scene.
Is there any footage where we can
see his face clearly?
It's blocked.
But notice his shoes and clothes.
Fifteen minutes later,
this person appeared again.
[Camera 01]
Xin Jiran appeared at the crime scene
and is a major suspect in the case.
Apply for a summons immediately.
Send more people to find him.
Yes.
Why are the police looking for you?
Something happened.
I can't explain it
in a few words right now.
Let's talk when we meet.
Let's meet at the usual place
at 9 p.m. tomorrow.
Why are you downstairs at my place?
Where are you going?
Benteng Internet Cafe.
The situation is beyond my expectations.
Stop looking for Han Pinmu from today on.
Stop all forms of investigation into him.
Why?
I'm worried about your safety.
The current situation is unclear.
Letting you act freely
is too irresponsible.
Don't worry.
I am willing to take the risk myself.
Still no.
This is an order.
But I already made an appointment with
Han Pinmu.
If I suddenly don't show up,
it will be even weirder.
Then go for the last time today.
Find an excuse.
Just say you'll be away for a while.
Don't go there anymore.
Okay.
Has Xin Jiran contacted you recently?
No.
I'll drop you off at the internet cafe.
Do as I say.
As for work, it depends on what you think.
If you really want to join
the Criminal Investigation Brigade,
I'll risk my old face
to get you in.
Okay.
Thank you, Sir.
Don't call me sir anymore.
Call me Zhao.
Or maybe Master.
But not necessarily.
We'll see when the time comes.
Thank you, Master.
Go.
Didn't you say you weren't coming?
Why are you here again?
I already asked someone else
to play with me.
Count me out.
I'll just watch a video and leave.
I have to pick up my mom.
If I go early, I'll just be waiting.
Even with such a little time,
you still want to delve into it.
With your perseverance,
you can do anything.
Alright, it's about time.
I'm leaving now.
Leaving already?
Wei.
How long has Li Cheng been here?
About ten minutes?
He wants to play even with so little time.
He's really addicted.
Where is Captain Fan?
Over there.
Captain Fan.
Luo made a major discovery.
The DNA from the blood on the wooden stick
at Song Laifu's crime scene
matches the skin tissue under the nails
of the third victim, Liu Xiaohua,
in the 312 Case
8 years ago.
The person with whom Song Laifu had
a confrontation before his death
is one of the suspects at large
from the 312 Case.
The police are all looking for you.
Does Song's death have anything
to do with you?
I was framed.
That afternoon.
I received a call.
The person said
they could provide clues about 312.
The meeting place was very remote.
I knew it could be a trap.
But first,
the meeting was during the day.
Second,
I was afraid of missing the opportunity.
So I went.
I didn't expect that
as soon as I arrived at the meeting place,
Song Laifu had already been killed.
I knew I couldn't explain it clearly,
so I left the scene immediately.
Who called you?
I don't know.
It didn't sound like
Han Pinmu.
They used an unregistered SIM card.
There are no clues at all.
Then why didn't you
report this to the police?
From the police's perspective,
I have a motive,
and I was at the scene.
They wouldn't let me go.
If you don't show up now,
it looks like you're fleeing from justice.
It'll be even harder to explain.
It doesn't matter.
I'm not afraid.
The truth will be found sooner or later.
Then why did you ask to meet me?
What do you want me to do?
Keep in touch with me privately,
and help me gather information
from the police.
Why not ask Zhao Ganzhe?
I told you on the phone.
I don't want to put him in
a difficult position.
He's a good person.
And you're not a good person.?
Have you ever seen a good person
who has been to prison?
Why did you go to prison
in the first place?
I don't want to talk about this.
You'll know later.
I need to know everything about you
to decide whether to help you or not.
8 years ago,
I...
I killed my son.
It hurts.
Xin Jiran, I'm your son!
I'm not a criminal!
I'm guilty.
I'm turning myself in.